Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[This drama is fictional, and any resemblance to real people or events is coincidental.]
[هذه الدراما خيالية، وأي تشابه مع أشخاص أو أحداث حقيقية هو محض مصادفة.]
[Episode 8] Come on!
[الحلقة 8] هيا!
Dad.
أب.
Excuse me, teachers.
عذرا أيها المعلمون.
We have a new driver for our shuttle bus from now on.
لدينا سائق جديد لحافلة النقل المكوكية الخاصة بنا من الآن فصاعدا.
Mr. Gil, come over here for a second.
السيد جيل، تعال إلى هنا لثانية واحدة.
Please take a moment to greet them.
من فضلك خذ لحظة لتحيتهم.
Oh, my.
أوه، يا إلهي.
Pleased to meet you.
ممتن لمقابلتك.
My name is Gil Ho Se.
اسمي جيل هو سي.
- Hello.
- مرحبا.
Let's all work well together this month.
دعونا جميعا نعمل معا بشكل جيد هذا الشهر.
- Nice to meet you.
- يسعدني أن ألتقي بك.
Was it difficult to memorize the children's addresses?
هل كان من الصعب حفظ عناوين الأطفال؟
No, that's part of my job.
لا، هذا جزء من وظيفتي.
Please take good care of the afternoon drop-offs too.
يرجى الاهتمام أيضًا بعملية التوصيل بعد الظهر.
Yes, Principal.
نعم سيدي المدير.
- Let's go in. - Let's go.
- دعنا ندخل. - دعنا نذهب.
A thief has appeared! Catch the thief!
ظهر لص! أمسكوا به!
Principal.
رئيسي.
Yes.
نعم.
How did you find Mr. Gil Ho Se?
كيف وجدت السيد جيل هو سي؟
From a job recruitment site.
من موقع توظيف.
Before his leg injury, he worked at several transport companies.
قبل إصابته في ساقه، كان يعمل في العديد من شركات النقل.
Could I see his resume?
هل يمكنني رؤية سيرته الذاتية؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Does something seem off?
هل يبدو أن هناك شيئا غير طبيعي؟
He's a stranger.
إنه غريب.
I'm concerned about my identity being exposed.
أنا قلق بشأن الكشف عن هويتي.
Oh, my.
أوه، يا إلهي.
I hadn't considered that.
لم أفكر في ذلك.
Let's go. It's in the principal's office.
هيا بنا. إنه في مكتب المدير.
Here it is.
ها هو.
I'll go teach the class, so take your time checking.
سأذهب لتدريس الفصل، لذا خذ وقتك في التحقق.
- Okay.
- حسنًا.
[Daehwang Transport]
[شركة دايهوانغ للنقل]
Daehwang Transport.
شركة دايهوانغ للنقل.
Hello, this is the Daehwang Transport office.
مرحبًا، هذا هو مكتب Daehwang للنقل.
I'd like to check the background of someone who worked there before.
أريد التحقق من خلفية الشخص الذي عمل هناك من قبل.
His name is Gil Ho Se.
اسمه جيل هو سي.
We keep records for only five years.
نحن نحتفظ بالسجلات لمدة خمس سنوات فقط.
If he worked here before that, it would be difficult to verify.
لو كان يعمل هنا قبل ذلك، فسيكون من الصعب التأكد من ذلك.
[Daehwang Transport 2015.10-2018.11] What was his employment period?
[Daehwang Transport 2015.10-2018.11] ما هي فترة عمله؟
[Work History] Ah, seven years ago.
[تاريخ العمل] آه، منذ سبع سنوات.
Okay, I understand, thank you.
حسنًا، فهمت، شكرًا لك.
Sorry, I thought the principal was here.
عذرا، اعتقدت أن المدير كان هنا.
How can I help you?
كيف يمكنني مساعدك؟
Oh, the vehicle needs its scheduled maintenance.
أوه، السيارة تحتاج إلى الصيانة الدورية.
So, I need to get it done before the afternoon drop-offs.
لذا، أحتاج إلى الانتهاء من ذلك قبل وقت التسليم بعد الظهر.
I'll let the principal know.
سأخبر المدير.
Oh, thank you.
أوه، شكرا لك.
- Thank you for your hard work. - Oh, okay.
- شكرا لك على عملك الجاد. - أوه حسنًا.
[Geumcheon Labor] Hurry up!
[عمل جومتشون] أسرع!
Captain.
قبطان.
That person over there. I've never seen him before.
هذا الشخص هناك. لم أره من قبل.
Is he a total newbie?
هل هو مبتدئ تماما؟
Oh, him?
أوه، هو؟
It's his first time here, but he's worked many other places.
إنها المرة الأولى له هنا، لكنه عمل في العديد من الأماكن الأخرى.
Try giving him a task, see how he does.
حاول أن تعطيه مهمة، وانظر كيف سيفعلها.
If he can't handle it,
إذا لم يتمكن من التعامل مع الأمر،
he'll be out right away, you know?
سوف يخرج على الفور، هل تعلم؟
By the way, what's going on with the Silver Town construction?
بالمناسبة، ما الذي يحدث مع بناء المدينة الفضية؟
We need to get it done so we can make a living.
نحن بحاجة إلى إنجاز ذلك حتى نتمكن من كسب لقمة العيش.
Ugh, just wait a bit.
أوه، فقط انتظر قليلا.
That's giving me headaches too.
وهذا يسبب لي الصداع أيضًا.
But I'm going to wrap it up before this winter.
ولكنني سأنهي الأمر قبل هذا الشتاء.
- I'm counting on you. - Yes.
- أنا أعتمد عليك. - نعم.
So exciting.
مثير للغاية.
Ms. Bu, are you going with us today?
السيدة بو، هل ستذهبين معنا اليوم؟
Yeah, I'm the one dropping them off today.
نعم، أنا من سيتركهم اليوم.
Oh, okay.
أوه، حسنا.
I'll close the door.
سأغلق الباب.
I love it most.
انا احبه كثيرا.
- Me too. - Absolutely love it.
- أنا أيضًا. - أحبه تمامًا.
Oh? Ms. Bu Se Mi's sitting in front of me.
أوه؟ السيدة بو سي مي تجلس أمامي.
Ms. Bu Se Mi's sitting next to me.
السيدة بو سي مي تجلس بجانبي.
- I'm riding with Ms. Bu. - But aren't you sitting in the back?
- أنا أركب مع السيدة بو. - ولكن ألا تجلس في الخلف؟
Today is great.
اليوم عظيم.
Alright, everyone.
حسنا، الجميع.
Shall we sing our kindergarten song together?
هل يجب علينا أن نغني أغنية روضة الأطفال معًا؟
- Yes.
- نعم.
- Start. - S, s, start.
- بداية. - س، س، بداية.
♪ Embracing the green energy of the mountains, our Muchang Iseon Kindergarten ♪
♪ احتضان الطاقة الخضراء للجبال، روضة أطفال موتشانج إيسيون الخاصة بنا ♪
[Muchang Supermarket]
[سوبر ماركت موتشانغ]
- Bye. - See you tomorrow.
- مع السلامة. - أراك غدا.
- Bye-bye. - See you.
- وداعا. - أراك لاحقا.
Hae Na's mom.
والدة هاي نا.
Mom, I'm home.
أمي، أنا في المنزل.
Huh? Oh.
هاه؟ أوه.
You came today, huh?
لقد أتيت اليوم، أليس كذلك؟
Ms. Jenny has a lot of work to do.
لدى السيدة جيني الكثير من العمل للقيام به.
I haven't seen those people before, right?
لم أرى هؤلاء الأشخاص من قبل، أليس كذلك؟
It's the busy season, so Seong Tae brought them.
إنه موسم مزدحم، لذلك أحضرهم سيونج تاي.
There's a shortage of workers in the countryside.
هناك نقص في العمال في الريف.
It must be a lot of work.
لا بد أن يكون هناك الكثير من العمل.
I'll go now.
سأذهب الآن.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Thank you. Miss, goodbye.
شكرا لك، آنسة، وداعا.
- Take care. - Okay.
- اعتني بنفسك. - حسنًا.
Ju Won's house is the last one.
بيت جو وون هو الأخير.
Mr. Gil, I'll get off with Ju Won this time.
السيد جيل، سأتخلص من جو وون هذه المرة.
Oh, you too?
أوه، وأنت أيضا؟
- Yes. - She lives with us.
- نعم. - إنها تعيش معنا.
Ah, really?
اه حقا؟
Wow, Ju Won. It must be nice.
واو، جو وون. لا بد أنه جميل.
We've arrived.
لقد وصلنا.
Alright, we've arrived.
حسنا، لقد وصلنا.
Ju Won, let's go home.
جو وون، دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Yes, Miss. Goodbye.
نعم يا آنسة وداعا.
See you tomorrow, Ju Won.
أراك غدا، جو وون.
Yes.
نعم.
- Bye. - See you.
- مع السلامة. - أراك لاحقًا.
Yes.
نعم.
Ju Won, let's go.
جو وون، دعنا نذهب.
[Psychopath]
[مختل عقليا]
She didn't even check the message.
ولم تتحقق حتى من الرسالة.
That woman's all talk, isn't she?
تلك المرأة مجرد كلام، أليس كذلك؟
That money from my daughter is all my money.
هذه الأموال من ابنتي هي كل أموالي.
Yeong Ran.
يونغ ران.
You're going to inherit that old man, Chairman Ga Sung Ho's wealth, right?
أنت سوف ترث ثروة ذلك الرجل العجوز، رئيس جا سونغ هو، أليس كذلك؟
I've thought about it.
لقد فكرت في هذا الأمر.
And how about 10 million won a month, on the condition that I stay quiet?
وماذا عن 10 ملايين وون شهريا، بشرط أن أبقى صامتا؟
I looked it up online, and that old man has a ton of assets.
لقد بحثت عن ذلك عبر الإنترنت، وهذا الرجل العجوز لديه الكثير من الأصول.
If we're talking about 10 million won a month
إذا كنا نتحدث عن 10 مليون وون شهريًا
for the maintenance of Chairman Ga Sung Ho's mother-in-law's dignity, that's a real bargain.
من أجل الحفاظ على كرامة حمات رئيس مجلس الإدارة جا سونغ هو، فهذه صفقة حقيقية.
Don't you agree?
ألا توافق؟
I'll give you a week.
سأعطيك اسبوعا.
Think carefully.
فكر جيدا.
Yeong Ran.
يونغ ران.
Lee Don seems to be playing games.
يبدو أن لي دون يلعب الألعاب.
[Seon Woo]
[سيون وو]
How long has he been holed up in the hotel?
كم من الوقت ظل محصورا في الفندق؟
Sis, it's me.
أختي، أنا.
Seon Woo.
سون وو.
Where are you right now?
أين أنت الآن؟
Shut up now and listen carefully.
أسكت الآن واستمع بعناية.
About those shares you have,
أما بالنسبة للأسهم التي لديك،
transfer all of them to me.
انقلهم جميعا إلي.
What does that even mean?
ماذا يعني هذا حتى؟
Don't pretend you don't know, again!
لا تتظاهر بأنك لا تعرف مرة أخرى!
Don't you remember that day?
ألا تتذكر ذلك اليوم؟
The day Ye Rim died.
اليوم الذي مات فيه يي ريم.
You were in New York, right?
لقد كنت في نيويورك، أليس كذلك؟
Well.
حسنًا.
I happen to have a video from that day.
لقد صادف أن لدي فيديو من ذلك اليوم.
Seon Woo.
سون وو.
Let's meet and talk.
دعونا نلتقي ونتحدث.
How about it?
ماذا عن ذلك؟
If you accept my offer, come to Suite 858, Sujeong Hotel, right now.
إذا كنت تقبل عرضي، تعال إلى جناح 858، فندق سوجيونج، الآن.
If you refuse my offer,
إذا رفضت عرضي،
I'll just send this to Kim Yeong Ran.
سأرسل هذا إلى كيم يونج ران.
Do as you will.
افعل ما تريد.
[Seon Woo]
[سيون وو]
Wow... These siblings, really...
واو... هؤلاء الأشقاء، حقًا...
Seon Woo is in Suite 858 at Sujeong Hotel.
سيون وو موجود في الجناح 858 في فندق سوجيونج.
No matter what it takes, bring him to me right now.
مهما كان الأمر، أحضره إلي الآن.
Yes, Professor.
نعم أستاذ.
[Ms. Bu Se Mi]
[السيدة بو سي مي]
[Gil Ho Se's Resume]
[السيرة الذاتية لجيل هو سي]
Yes?
نعم؟
Madam.
سيدتي.
Ga Seon Woo has decisive evidence
لدى جا سون وو أدلة حاسمة
that Ga Seon Yeong is involved in Ye Rim's death.
أن جا سون يونغ متورطة في وفاة يي ريم.
Is that evidence reliable?
هل هذا الدليل موثوق؟
Yes, I've verified it.
نعم لقد تأكدت من ذلك.
If we secure this evidence,
إذا حصلنا على هذا الدليل،
this game will end quickly without any bloodshed.
ستنتهي هذه اللعبة بسرعة دون أي سفك للدماء.
Yes, understood.
نعم، فهمت.
For now, please secure the evidence, Attorney Lee.
في الوقت الحالي، يرجى تأمين الأدلة، المحامي لي.
But I'll follow through on the promise I made to Chairman.
ولكنني سأنفذ الوعد الذي قطعته للرئيس.
Understood, Madam.
مفهوم سيدتي.
Things are turning in our favor,
الأمور تتحول لصالحنا،
so please stay alive.
لذا يرجى البقاء على قيد الحياة.
What's with the bouquet?
ما الأمر مع الباقة؟
- Is it for confession? - Be quiet.
- هل هذا من أجل الإعتراف؟ - إصمت.
Oh, jeez.
أوه، يا إلهي.
Where is she rushing off to?
إلى أين تتجه؟
Hey, I've got an emergency. I'll be back.
مرحباً، لديّ حالة طارئة. سأعود.
Good luck with your confession.
أتمنى لك حظا سعيدا مع اعترافك.
Dong Min, hey.
دونغ مين، مهلا.
Where did she go?
أين ذهبت؟
Corn.
حبوب ذرة.
When the corn grows tall, tall, tall,
عندما ينمو الذرة طويلًا، طويلًا، طويلًا،
pick the corn, knock, knock, knock,
قطف الذرة، دق، دق، دق،
peel off the husk, shuck, shuck, shuck,
انزع القشرة، انزع، انزع، انزع،
then the corn is plump, plump, plump!
ثم الذرة تصبح ممتلئة، ممتلئة، ممتلئة!
You startled me.
لقد فاجأتني.
Ms. Baek Hye Ji.
السيدة بايك هيه جي.
Make some noise when you walk!
اصنع بعض الضوضاء عندما تمشي!
I'm the owner of this house,
أنا صاحب هذا البيت
yet I feel like a squatter in my own home.
ولكنني أشعر وكأنني مستوطن في منزلي.
Oh, what a scare.
أوه، ما هذا الخوف.
Nobody here is normal, including Madam.
لا يوجد أحد طبيعي هنا، بما في ذلك السيدة.
Ugh, what should I do?
أوه، ماذا يجب أن أفعل؟
[Practical Assignment for 'Field Practice'] I need to upload this quickly.
[الواجب العملي لـ 'التدريب الميداني'] أحتاج إلى تحميل هذا بسرعة.
The moon today
القمر اليوم
is dark tonight.
الليلة مظلمة.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Answer me!
يجيبني!
Miss.
يفتقد.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
There...
هناك...
He disappeared near here, right?
لقد اختفى بالقرب من هنا، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
By the way, where are we?
بالمناسبة، أين نحن؟
It's the lodging for the farmhands.
إنه مكان إقامة لعمال المزرعة.
I think the only place he could run to is here.
أعتقد أن المكان الوحيد الذي يمكنه الركض إليه هو هنا.
I'll go check it out.
سأذهب للتحقق من ذلك.
Oh, wait a minute.
أوه، انتظر دقيقة.
This is the men's lodging.
هذا هو سكن الرجال.
I'll go check. Wait here for a bit.
سأذهب للتحقق. انتظر هنا قليلاً.
No, that's not it.
لا، ليس هذا هو الأمر.
It's not.
ليست كذلك.
Who are you looking for?
من تبحث عنه؟
Oh, nothing.
اوه لا شيء.
There is someone suspicious, though.
هناك شخص مشبوه، رغم ذلك.
It's late today,
لقد تأخر الوقت اليوم
so I'll check with Seong Tae tomorrow.
لذا سأتحقق مع Seong Tae غدًا.
Let's call it a day for now.
فلنتوقف عن هذا اليوم الآن.
That person had a scar on their collarbone.
وكان لدى هذا الشخص ندبة على عظم الترقوة.
It would be useful if you remembered that too.
سيكون من المفيد لو تذكرت ذلك أيضًا.
A scar on the collarbone...
ندبة على عظم الترقوة
Got it.
فهمتها.
Wait.
انتظر.
Give me your phone.
أعطني هاتفك.
My phone?
هاتفي؟
Why do you need my phone?
لماذا تحتاج هاتفي؟
How am I saved in your contacts?
كيف يتم حفظي في جهات الاتصال الخاصة بك؟
Jeon Dong Min.
جون دونغ مين.
Jeon Dong Min?
جون دونغ مين؟
Not Mr. Jeon Dong Min, not Mr. Jeon, not Teacher.
ليس السيد جون دونج مين، وليس السيد جون، وليس المعلم.
You really typed it honestly, huh?
لقد كتبتها بصدق حقًا، أليس كذلك؟
I set up a speed dial for you.
لقد قمت بإعداد اتصال سريع لك.
If there's an emergency, just press 1.
في حالة الطوارئ، فقط اضغط على الرقم 1.
I'll get there faster than the police, okay?
سأصل إلى هناك أسرع من الشرطة، حسنًا؟
No need for this stuff.
لا حاجة لهذه الأشياء.
Wow, her personality is something else.
واو، شخصيتها شيء آخر.
Tae Min, what are you doing there?
تاي مين ماذا تفعل هناك؟
Oh, this, this thing.
أوه، هذا، هذا الشيء.
The one you mentioned last time.
الذي ذكرته في المرة الماضية.
Tae Min.
تاي مين.
Yes.
نعم.
You like me, right?
أنت تحبني، أليس كذلك؟
Well.
حسنًا.
Oh, that's...
أوه، هذا...
Oh, wait.
أوه، انتظر.
No.
لا.
No, not now. No.
لا، ليس الآن.
Baek Hye Ji.
بايك هيه جي.
Yes.
نعم.
I admire her.
أنا معجب بها.
General.
عام.
Why?
لماذا؟
People don't confess like that these days.
الناس لا يعترفون بهذه الطريقة هذه الأيام.
It's old-fashioned.
إنه من الطراز القديم.
Old-fashioned?
الطراز القديم؟
I don't care about what's trendy.
لا يهمني ما هو عصري.
Tae Min's been worried sick about you.
لقد كان تاي مين قلقًا عليك كثيرًا.
Just remember that.
فقط تذكر ذلك.
This...
هذا...
Huh? General.
هاه؟ يا جنرال.
- Tae Min. - Yes.
- تاي مين. - نعم.
I'm tired. I'm going inside.
أنا متعب. سأذهب إلى الداخل.
Wait.
انتظر.
General! General!
جنرال! جنرال!
Please, was that a confession or not?
من فضلك هل كان هذا اعترافا أم لا؟
What do I do?
ماذا أفعل؟
Mom.
أم.
[Answer, Door Open]
[الجواب، الباب مفتوح]
Ugh, where are they?
أوه، أين هم؟
Why aren't they here yet?
لماذا هم ليسوا هنا بعد؟
I knew Ga Seon Yeong wouldn't come herself.
لقد عرفت أن جا سون يونغ لن تأتي بنفسها.
I can't let Ga Seon Woo get caught.
لا أستطيع أن أترك جا سون وو يتم القبض عليه.
Vice President.
نائب الرئيس.
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
[Answer, Door Open] Open up.
[الجواب، الباب مفتوح] افتح.
What?
ماذا؟
Only Secretary Han came?
هل جاء السكرتير هان فقط؟
Shoot!
أطلق النار!
Yeah.
نعم.
My sister always does this.
أختي تفعل هذا دائمًا.
You think I don't know you're trying to lock me up and kill me like Dad?
هل تعتقد أنني لا أعرف أنك تحاول سجني وقتلي مثل أبي؟
Come out.
يخرج.
Vice President.
نائب الرئيس.
Huh?
هاه؟
Excuse me, let me get it for you.
عذرا، دعني أحصل عليه لك.
- Fire!
- نار!
Fire, fire!
نار، نار!
- Fire, fire! - Get away from the fire.
- نار، نار! - ابتعد عن النار.
Get away from the fire.
ابتعد عن النار
Go that way.
اذهب في هذا الطريق.
Fire!
نار!
- Darn. Get out quickly! - Oh, no.
- اللعنة. اخرج بسرعة! - أوه، لا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
You want to give it a shot?
هل تريد أن تجرب ذلك؟
I'm not going to sit still anymore.
لن أجلس ساكنا بعد الآن.
What is that?
ما هذا؟
It's a list of today's tasks.
إنها قائمة بالمهام اليومية.
First, let's go to Seong Tae,
أولاً، دعنا نذهب إلى Seong Tae،
get information about people who came from outside.
الحصول على معلومات عن الأشخاص الذين جاءوا من الخارج.
Okay.
تمام.
About that guy from yesterday.
عن ذلك الرجل من أمس.
You mentioned he had a scar on his collarbone, right?
لقد ذكرت أنه كان لديه ندبة على عظم الترقوة، أليس كذلك؟
Which side was it on?
على أي جانب كان؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Answer me!
يجيبني!
- The left. - Left.
- اليسار.
A scar on the left collarbone.
ندبة على عظم الترقوة الأيسر.
Probably someone athletic.
ربما شخص رياضي.
I'll keep a close eye out.
سأبقي عيني على ذلك عن كثب.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
We need to do it as soon as possible.
نحن بحاجة إلى القيام بذلك في أقرب وقت ممكن.
Okay?
تمام؟
Seong Tae.
سيونغ تاي.
It's just that I heard from someone
فقط سمعت من شخص ما
that your people have a great reputation for doing good work.
أن شعبك يتمتع بسمعة طيبة في أداء العمل الجيد.
They really are good.
إنهم جيدون حقا.
So, by the way,
لذا، بالمناسبة،
if you have any contact details or personal info, could you share them with me?
إذا كان لديك أي تفاصيل اتصال أو معلومات شخصية، هل يمكنك مشاركتها معي؟
You're just asking for that?
هل تطلب هذا فقط؟
By the way, Hae Na left her pencil case yesterday.
بالمناسبة، تركت هاى نا علبة أقلامها أمس.
I was thinking of dropping it off when I head to the supermarket.
كنت أفكر في تركها عندما أتوجه إلى السوبر ماركت.
I'll text you right away.
سأرسل لك رسالة على الفور.
Hurry up, come on.
اسرع، هيا.
Oh, not bad at all.
أوه، ليس سيئا على الإطلاق.
We should split up here.
ينبغي لنا أن ننفصل هنا.
What?
ماذا؟
We just teamed up, and you're already leaving?
لقد تعاوننا للتو، وأنت تغادر بالفعل؟
I have to get to work.
يجب علي أن أذهب إلى العمل.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
Since I'm free, I'll look around a bit more.
بما أنني متفرغ، سأبحث قليلاً.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Excuse me, by any chance,
عذرا، بالصدفة،
is there anyone here
هل يوجد أحد هنا
who has a scar on their collarbone?
من لديه ندبة على عظم الترقوة؟
Someone with a dark face and a tall build?
شخص ذو وجه داكن وبنية طويلة؟
Have you worked with anyone like that before?
هل عملت مع شخص مثله من قبل؟
No.
لا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Jeong Woo!
جونغ وو!
Oh, Dong Min.
أوه، دونغ مين.
[Muchang Police Station] What brings you here so early?
[مركز شرطة موتشانغ] ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا في وقت مبكر جدًا؟
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Well, actually,
حسنا، في الواقع،
I was walking last night
كنت أمشي الليلة الماضية
and saw a suspicious person lurking at the village entrance.
ورأيت شخصًا مشبوهًا يتربص عند مدخل القرية.
Oh really? Why didn't you report it?
أوه حقًا؟ لماذا لم تبلغ عن ذلك؟
Please do more night patrols.
يرجى القيام بدوريات ليلية أكثر.
Got it, got it. We'll step up patrols.
فهمت، فهمت. سنكثّف الدوريات.
Keep up the good work.
استمر في العمل الجيد.
- Yes. - Bye.
- نعم. - مع السلامة.
Let's keep up our night patrols.
دعونا نواصل دورياتنا الليلية.
Patrols are stronger, list is ready.
الدوريات أصبحت أقوى، والقائمة جاهزة.
Now, I just need to protect Ms. Bu Se Mi.
الآن، كل ما أحتاجه هو حماية السيدة بو سي مي.
Miss.
يفتقد.
There's a guy named Lee Se Joon here.
هناك رجل اسمه لي سي جون هنا.
He works night shifts every day.
يعمل في نوبات ليلية كل يوم.
We should check him out.
ينبغي علينا التحقق منه.
Okay.
تمام.
Stay here. I'll go investigate.
ابقى هنا. سأذهب للتحقيق.
Miss!
يفتقد!
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
He just went into Muchang Supermarket Alley.
لقد ذهب للتو إلى زقاق سوبر ماركت موتشانج.
I think it's him.
أعتقد أنه هو.
Got it, I'm on my way.
فهمت، أنا في طريقي.
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
Get up.
استيقظ.
It hurts.
إنه يؤلمني.
He has no scar.
ليس لديه ندبة.
Hey, what's wrong with you guys?
مهلا، ما هو الخطأ معكم يا رفاق؟
It's you, right?
أنت، أليس كذلك؟
You were the one who attacked her yesterday, right?
أنت من هاجمها بالأمس، أليس كذلك؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Didn't you break the CCTV?
ألم تكسر كاميرا المراقبة؟
I heard they were hiring at Mu Si Market,
سمعت أنهم يقومون بالتوظيف في سوق مو سي،
I just did what I was told and got paid for it.
لقد فعلت ما قيل لي وحصلت على أجر مقابل ذلك.
Man, I knew something was off.
يا رجل، كنت أعلم أن هناك شيئا خاطئا.
Does that person limp?
هل يعرج هذا الشخص؟
We only communicated via phone.
لقد تواصلنا فقط عبر الهاتف.
I don't know anything about him.
لا أعرف عنه شيئا.
I just did what they told me, they said I'd get 50,000 for each CCTV I broke,
لقد فعلت ما أخبروني به، قالوا إنني سأحصل على 50 ألفًا مقابل كل كاميرا مراقبة أكسرها،
so I worked hard for it.
لذلك عملت بجد من أجل ذلك.
Then how did you know the CCTV routes?
ثم كيف عرفت مسارات كاميرات المراقبة؟
That guy sent me all the details.
لقد أرسل لي هذا الرجل كافة التفاصيل.
Including all the patrol routes.
بما في ذلك جميع طرق الدوريات.
[Mu Si Market]
[سوق مو سي]
Wow, he's fast.
واو، إنه سريع.
Ah, we lost him.
اه، لقد فقدناه.
By the way, earlier,
بالمناسبة، في وقت سابق،
you asked if he was limping, right?
لقد سألته إذا كان يعرج، أليس كذلك؟
Are you talking about that driver?
هل تتحدث عن هذا السائق؟
Yes.
نعم.
The only recent newcomers to Muchang
الوافدون الجدد الوحيدون إلى موتشانج
are the driver and seasonal farm workers.
هم السائقون والعمال الزراعيون الموسميون.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Hey, let's call it a day.
مهلا، فلننهي هذا اليوم.
Okay.
تمام.
[Gil Ho Se's Resume] Why hasn't he checked this?
[السيرة الذاتية لـ جيل هو سي] لماذا لم يتحقق من هذا؟
[Attorney Lee]
[المحامي لي]
The subscriber you dialed is unavailable. You will be connected to voicemail.
المشترك الذي طلبته غير متاح. سيتم توصيلك بالبريد الصوتي.
Who the heck are you guys?
من أنتم أيها الرجال؟
Hey.
يا.
Where's Ga Seon Woo?
أين جا سون وو؟
That's what I want to know.
هذا ما أريد أن أعرفه.
Ah, that lunatic.
اه، هذا المجنون.
Boss, what about our money?
يا رئيس، ماذا عن أموالنا؟
Do you know who I am?
هل تعرف من أنا؟
Attorney Lee Don.
المحامي لي دون.
We're not in the mood for games.
نحن لسنا في مزاج للألعاب.
Why?
لماذا؟
Did Ga Seon Woo rip you off?
هل قام جا سون وو بخداعك؟
You punk.
أنت بانك.
People are all talking down to me.
الناس كلهم ​​يتكلمون معي باستخفاف.
I'll give you all the money Ga Seon Woo owes.
سأعطيك كل الأموال التي يدين بها جا سون وو.
I'm loaded.
أنا محملة.
But why should we trust you?
ولكن لماذا يجب علينا أن نثق بك؟
How did you find me?
كيف وجدتني؟
That's our specialty.
هذا هو تخصصنا.
Really?
حقًا؟
I'm looking for Ga Seon Woo too.
أنا أبحث عن جا سون وو أيضًا.
100 million if you find Ga Seon Woo.
100 مليون إذا وجدت جا سون وو.
Until then10 million deduction daily. Deal?
حتى ذلك الحين، خصم ١٠ ملايين يوميًا. اتفاق؟
Ah, this is frustrating.
أه، هذا محبط.
Another day's already passing.
يوم آخر يمر بالفعل.
Are you joking, punk?
هل أنت تمزح أيها البانك؟
Soon, 10 million won will be deducted.
سيتم خصم 10 مليون وون قريبًا.
Pay the deposit of 50 million won.
دفع وديعة قدرها 50 مليون وون.
I got it, so let me go.
لقد حصلت عليه، لذا دعني أذهب.
Hey.
يا.
50 million won for the deposit.
50 مليون وون للإيداع.
Transfer it.
نقله.
[Ms. Bu Se Mi]
[السيدة بو سي مي]
[Gil Ho Se's Resume]
[السيرة الذاتية لجيل هو سي]
[Shuttle Bus Driver]
[سائق حافلة النقل المكوكية]
[Mid-40s, had an accident and injured his leg]
[منتصف الأربعينيات من عمره، تعرض لحادث وأُصيب في ساقه]
[Gil Ho Se]
[جيل هو سي]
Can you find another person?
هل يمكنك العثور على شخص آخر؟
An additional 100 million won.
100 مليون وون إضافية.
Same terms.
نفس الشروط.
Deal.
اتفاق.
Transfer it.
نقله.
Come this way.
تعال من هذا الطريق.
I heard you do a great job here, so I came.
لقد سمعت أنك تقوم بعمل عظيم هنا، لذلك أتيت.
I need a passport.
أحتاج إلى جواز سفر.
How long does it take?
كم من الوقت تستغرق؟
Passport takes 3 days.
جواز السفر يستغرق 3 أيام.
It's not available for the U.S. or Europe,
إنه غير متاح للولايات المتحدة أو أوروبا،
but no problem for Southeast Asia.
ولكن لا توجد مشكلة بالنسبة لجنوب شرق آسيا.
No problem with money,
لا مشكلة مع المال،
so the faster, the better.
فكلما كان أسرع كان أفضل.
Rushing leads to mistakes.
التسرع يؤدي إلى الأخطاء.
I said I got it.
قلت أنني حصلت عليه.
Just meet the deadline.
فقط إلتزم بالموعد النهائي.
Come back in 3 days.
العودة بعد 3 أيام.
Ms. Bu Se Mi, there's an announcement.
السيدة بو سي مي، هناك إعلان.
This week, a village volleyball competition will be held at the elementary school playground.
سيتم هذا الأسبوع عقد مسابقة الكرة الطائرة بالقرية في ملعب المدرسة الابتدائية.
Please attend.
الرجاء الحضور.
There's an afterparty too.
هناك حفلة لاحقة أيضًا.
Let's celebrate together and have dinner.
دعونا نحتفل معًا ونتناول العشاء.
- Principal. - Yes?
- مدير المدرسة. - نعم؟
Are there people coming from other villages?
هل هناك أشخاص يأتون من قرى أخرى؟
Well,
حسنًا،
Dong Min and Jeong Woo from YBS,
دونغ مين وجيونغ وو من YBS،
and Dongwaru and upper village chief from OBS.
ودونجوارو ورئيس القرية العليا من OBS.
Mainly upper village folks.
معظمهم من سكان القرية العليا.
Got it.
فهمتها.
Yes.
نعم.
Good morning, Principal.
صباح الخير يا مدير.
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
Ms. Baek Hye Ji.
السيدة بايك هيه جي.
Let's talk for a minute.
دعونا نتحدث لمدة دقيقة.
I need to prepare materials before class.
أحتاج إلى تحضير المواد قبل الفصل الدراسي.
I'll come to Strawberry Class after class.
سوف آتي إلى صف الفراولة بعد انتهاء الدرس.
Have a good class.
أتمنى لك درسًا جيدًا.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
See you then.
أراك لاحقا.
Okay.
تمام.
Gimme a bite.
أعطني قضمة.
- No. - Just one bite.
- لا. - فقط لقمة واحدة.
- No, I'll eat it all. - One bite.
- لا، سآكله كله. - لقمة واحدة.
Just one bite.
لقمة واحدة فقط
Mister, I'm sorry.
سيدي، أنا آسف.
No, are you okay?
لا هل انت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I can change clothes, so it's fine.
أستطيع تغيير ملابسي، لذا فالأمر جيد.
Oh, no.
أوه لا.
Oh, you spilled it.
أوه، لقد سكبت ذلك.
Running's dangerous, right?
الجري خطير، أليس كذلك؟
Let's go in.
دعنا ندخل.
Go inside and play.
اذهب إلى الداخل والعب.
You got me.
لقد حصلت علي.
Now, you recognize my footsteps?
الآن هل تعرفت على خطواتي؟
Ms. Baek Hye Ji.
السيدة بايك هيه جي.
Why did you follow me last night?
لماذا تبعتني الليلة الماضية؟
Are you spying on me?
هل تتجسس علي؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm spying on you.
أنا أتجسس عليك.
I won't ask who told you to do this,
لن أسأل من قال لك أن تفعل هذا،
but now stop playing games and leave Muchang.
لكن الآن توقف عن لعب الألعاب واترك موتشانج.
I don't want to care about you anymore either.
أنا أيضًا لا أريد أن أهتم بك بعد الآن.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Oh, it's Hye Ji.
أوه، إنها هيه جي.
[Baek Hye Ji]
[بايك هيه جي]
Call me in 30 minutes.
اتصل بي خلال 30 دقيقة.
Yes, Miss.
نعم يا آنسة.
Are you heading home?
هل انت متجه الى المنزل؟
Yes.
نعم.
Then, please give me a ride home.
إذن، من فضلك أعطني توصيلة إلى المنزل.
Sure, get in.
بالتأكيد، ادخل.
- Thank you. - Yes.
- شكرا لك. - نعم.
Alright, let's go.
حسنا، دعنا نذهب.
Miss, what are you looking for?
آنسة، ماذا تبحثين عنه؟
Well, I've always wondered about the shuttle bus's front seats.
حسنًا، لقد تساءلت دائمًا عن المقاعد الأمامية لحافلة النقل المكوكية.
Nothing special.
لا شيء خاص.
Where do you live, Mr. Gil?
أين تعيش يا سيد جيل؟
Why ask that?
لماذا تسأل ذلك؟
Well, I came down here and have been staying at the principal's place.
حسنًا، لقد جئت إلى هنا وأقيم في منزل المدير.
I'm trying to find a place to live.
أحاول العثور على مكان للعيش فيه.
But I just got a place through someone I know.
لكنني حصلت للتو على مكان من خلال شخص أعرفه.
Oh?
أوه؟
Do you know someone here? Who?
هل تعرف أحدًا هنا؟ من؟
Well, I've met most people in this town at the village welcome party,
حسنًا، لقد التقيت بمعظم الأشخاص في هذه المدينة في حفل الترحيب بالقرية،
so I know everyone in this neighborhood, more or less.
لذا فأنا أعرف الجميع في هذا الحي، أكثر أو أقل.
Oh, I see.
أوه، أرى.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
You really wanna know?
هل تريد حقا أن تعرف؟
30, 29, 28, 27.
30، 29، 28، 27.
26, 25, 24, 23...
26، 25، 24، 23...
No way...
مستحيل...
Is it the village chief?
هل هو رئيس القرية؟
It's the village chief.
إنه رئيس القرية.
Ah, right.
اه، صحيح.
How did you know?
كيف عرفت؟
Everything and everyone here
كل شيء وكل شخص هنا
goes through the village chief.
يمر عبر رئيس القرية.
Right.
يمين.
By the way, these days,
بالمناسبة، في هذه الأيام،
the trend is for tough guys to leave one or two buttons undone on their shirts.
الاتجاه هو أن يترك الرجال الأقوياء زرًا أو زرين على قمصانهم مفتوحين.
Aren't you hot?
هل أنت حار؟
I'm a bit sensitive to the cold.
أنا حساس قليلاً للبرد.
2, 1, time's up.
2، 1، انتهى الوقت.
Hello, Tae Min?
مرحباً تاي مين؟
Yes, I'll be down soon.
نعم، سأنزل قريبا.
Okay.
تمام.
Ah, yes. Huh?
اه نعم. هاه؟
What was that?
ماذا كان هذا؟
[20-19, Eumjeon-ro 28beon-gil, Muchang-myeon, Muchang County, Gyeongnam]
[20-19، Eumjeon-ro 28beon-gil، Muchang-myeon، مقاطعة Muchang، Gyeongnam]
[Professor, I'll handle it tomorrow.]
[أستاذ، سأتعامل مع هذا الأمر غدًا.]
She changed her identity?
هل غيرت هويتها؟
Then if that woman dies instead of Kim Yeong Ran,
ثم إذا ماتت تلك المرأة بدلاً من كيم يونج ران،
what happens to Kim Yeong Ran?
ماذا يحدث لكيم يونغ ران؟
If a missing adult shows no signs of life for five years,
إذا لم يظهر الشخص البالغ المفقود أي علامات على الحياة لمدة خمس سنوات،
they're declared dead.
لقد تم إعلان وفاتهم.
If Kim Yeong Ran dies now, it'll complicate things.
إذا مات كيم يونج ران الآن، فإن الأمور سوف تتعقد.
Maybe it wouldn't be such a bad thing for someone else to die.
ربما لن يكون الأمر سيئًا جدًا أن يموت شخص آخر.
[Mom]
[أم]
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Come pick me up, Yeong Ran.
تعال لتأخذني، يونغ ران.
Miss, something wrong?
آنسة، هناك خطأ ما؟
Can you take me to Dongwaru?
هل يمكنك أن تأخذني إلى دونجوارو؟
Sure, get in.
بالتأكيد، ادخل.
Madam!
سيدتي!
Time to go home!
حان وقت العودة إلى المنزل!
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
My daughter will pick me up.
ابنتي سوف تأتي لأخذي.
Madam, how about the bill...
سيدتي، ماذا عن الفاتورة...
Don't you know my daughter?
ألا تعرف ابنتي؟
My daughter, Kim... Se Mi.
ابنتي كيم...سي مي.
You mean Ms. Bu Se Mi, right?
هل تقصد السيدة بو سي مي، أليس كذلك؟
No one here gets it on the first try.
لا أحد هنا يحصل عليه في المحاولة الأولى.
Hello, you come for her?
مرحبا هل أتيت لها؟
Sorry.
آسف.
She hasn't paid yet.
لم تدفع بعد
I'll pay you when I get home.
سأدفع لك عندما أعود إلى المنزل.
Mom, let's go.
أمي هيا بنا نذهب.
Mom, why did you drink so much alone?
أمي لماذا شربت كثيرًا وحدك؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
This town's weird.
هذه المدينة غريبة.
No one here gets it on the first try.
لا أحد هنا يحصل عليه في المحاولة الأولى.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
[Changhyeon Police Station]
[مركز شرطة تشانغهيون]
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
- Oh, my. - Found her collapsed on the street.
- أوه، يا إلهي. - وجدتها منهارة في الشارع.
She looks like she's heavily drunk.
إنها تبدو وكأنها في حالة سكر شديد.
Oh, she drank a lot, couldn't even speak properly.
أوه، لقد شربت كثيرًا، ولم تكن قادرة حتى على التحدث بشكل صحيح.
Do you know her?
هل تعرفها؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Kim Yeong Ran.
كيم يونغ ران.
My daughter.
ابنتي.
My daughter, Kim Yeong Ran.
ابنتي كيم يونغ ران.
[Teacher ID: Bu Se Mi] She's a stranger.
[معرف المعلم: بو سي مي] إنها غريبة.
She drank too much, I guess.
لقد شربت كثيرًا، على ما أعتقد.
Must've been tough. Thank you.
لا بد أن الأمر كان صعبًا. شكرًا لك.
We'll ensure her safe return once sober.
سنضمن عودتها سالمة بعد تعافيها.
Please take care of her.
من فضلك اعتني بها.
Hey!
يا!
Ma'am.
سيدتي.
Get your act together and straighten up your life.
قم بتنظيم أمورك وقم بتقويم حياتك.
Don't make your kids suffer.
لا تجعل أطفالك يعانون.
Kim Yeong Ran!
كيم يونغ ران!
Wait, Miss.
انتظري يا آنسة.
Is it okay to leave her like this?
هل يجوز تركها هكذا؟
Why?
لماذا؟
I'm a bit worried.
أنا قلقة بعض الشيء.
About what?
عن ما؟
What exactly are you worried about?
ما الذي يقلقك بالضبط؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Do you think I went too far?
هل تعتقد أنني ذهبت بعيدا جدا؟
The theft charge they're blasting on the news.
تهمة السرقة التي يتحدثون عنها في الأخبار.
I didn't steal the sanitary pads.
لم أسرق الفوط الصحية.
I considered stealing, but changed my mind and put them back.
لقد فكرت في السرقة، ولكن غيرت رأيي وأعدتها.
But I got caught at the worst possible moment.
لكنني وقعت في أسوأ لحظة ممكنة.
That convenience store owner pinned every theft on me.
لقد حمّلني صاحب متجر البقالة مسؤولية كل السرقة.
Then he demanded settlement money.
ثم طالب بتسوية مالية.
Do you know what Mom said when she showed up?
هل تعلم ماذا قالت أمي عندما ظهرت؟
'Yeong Ran, just go to juvie for a while.'
"يونغ ران، اذهبي إلى دار الأحداث لفترة من الوقت."
'I can't afford to pay.'
"لا أستطيع تحمل تكاليف الدفع."
That's just cruel, you know?
هذا قاسي جدًا، هل تعلم؟
Kim Yeong Ran!
كيم يونغ ران!
Ah, you wicked...
أه، أنت شرير...
Let's go home now.
دعونا نذهب إلى المنزل الآن.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Oh, my.
أوه، يا إلهي.
Honey.
عسل.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Oh, no, we're late.
أوه لا، لقد تأخرنا.
Hey, lift it up. Quickly.
هيا، ارفعها بسرعة.
One, two, three.
واحد اثنين ثلاثة.
Hey, Tae Min.
مرحبا، تيمين.
Okay.
تمام.
Honey.
عسل.
Principal.
رئيسي.
- This... - Oh, Mr. Gil.
- هذا... - أوه، السيد جيل.
- You can leave it here. - Hello.
- يمكنك تركه هنا. - مرحبا.
It's really trendy these days.
إنه أمر عصري حقًا هذه الأيام.
Oh, hello.
أوه، مرحبا.
Jenny, take some chairs over there.
جيني، خذي بعض الكراسي إلى هناك.
More this way.
المزيد بهذه الطريقة.
Okay.
تمام.
Ms. Choi, take a photo for me.
السيدة تشوي، التقطي لي صورة.
Ready?
مستعد؟
One, two, three.
واحد اثنين ثلاثة.
Anyway, our chairman's taste was so refined.
على أية حال، كان ذوق رئيسنا راقيا للغاية.
Hey, how much could we get selling these secondhand?
مرحبًا، كم يمكننا الحصول عليه من بيع هذه الأشياء المستعملة؟
Probably around 30 million won?
ربما حوالي 30 مليون وون؟
That much?
هذا القدر؟
Hey, selling just a few of these could beat our annual salary.
مرحبًا، بيع عدد قليل منها قد يفوق راتبنا السنوي.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
We can't find the will, and there's no money coming in.
لم نتمكن من العثور على الإرادة، وليس هناك أموال قادمة.
Anyway, I have to give you credit for your cleverness.
على أية حال، لا بد لي من أن أشكرك على ذكائك.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
It's a compliment. A compliment!
إنها مجاملة. مجاملة!
Hey, you take that photo.
مهلا، التقط تلك الصورة.
Ah, I said it's a compliment. Really!
آه، قلتُ إنها مجاملة. حقًا!
Being the lady of this house, I'd like some liquor...
باعتباري سيدة هذا المنزل، أود الحصول على بعض الخمور...
What's liquor? Sounds so old-fashioned.
ما هو الخمر؟ يبدو قديم الطراز.
Whiskey.
ويسكي.
Whether it's whiskey or liquor, it's all the same.
سواء كان الويسكي أو الخمور، كل شيء هو نفسه.
Butler, you went to Gukmin School, right?
بتلر، لقد ذهبت إلى مدرسة جوكمين، أليس كذلك؟
Yeah.
نعم.
I went to elementary school.
ذهبت إلى المدرسة الابتدائية.
The generation gap...
الفجوة بين الأجيال...
Yeah, you're so amazing.
نعم، أنت مذهلة جدًا.
Alright then.
حسنا إذن.
Should I post a photo after so long?
هل يجب أن أنشر صورة بعد كل هذه المدة؟
[Resume] Restaurant assistant, housekeeper, childcare aide.
[السيرة الذاتية] مساعد مطعم، مدبرة منزل، مساعدة رعاية الأطفال.
Laundry duty.
واجب الغسيل.
Madam, where should I put this?
سيدتي أين أضع هذا؟
Madam...
سيدتي...
Yeah...
نعم...
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
Put the Hanwoo beef in the fridge's third compartment.
ضعي لحم هانوو في الحجرة الثالثة من الثلاجة.
And place the pears in the fridge's bottom drawer.
ثم ضعي الكمثرى في الدرج السفلي من الثلاجة.
Leave the wild pine mushrooms here on the table.
اترك فطر الصنوبر البري هنا على الطاولة.
We'll have them for dinner later.
سوف نتناولهم على العشاء لاحقًا.
Nice.
لطيف - جيد.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
It's okay! It's okay!
لا بأس! لا بأس!
Good job.
أحسنت.
Enjoy your meal.
أتمنى لك وجبة شهية.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Ms. Bu, hurry up and sit down to eat.
السيدة بو، اسرعي واجلسي لتناول الطعام.
I'll eat later.
سوف آكل لاحقا.
Enjoy your meal.
أتمنى لك وجبة شهية.
[Gil Ho Se, Inmate ID Card]
[جيل هو سي، بطاقة هوية السجين]
[Gil Ho Se's Resume]
[السيرة الذاتية لجيل هو سي]
[Mid-40s, shuttle-bus driver, left leg injured in an accident]
[في منتصف الأربعينيات من عمره، سائق حافلة نقل مكوكية، أصيب في ساقه اليسرى في حادث]
Apple Class and Strawberry Class, enjoy your meal.
درس التفاح ودرس الفراولة، استمتع بوجبتك.
- Yes.
- نعم.
It's delicious.
إنه لذيذ.
[Attorney Lee] The meat is so delicious.
[المحامي لي] اللحوم لذيذة جدًا.
Just let me know if you need more.
فقط اسمح لي أن أعرف إذا كنت بحاجة إلى المزيد.
Okay.
تمام.
It's delicious.
إنه لذيذ.
Enjoy your meal.
أتمنى لك وجبة شهية.
Yes, it's me.
نعم، أنا.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Madam, I think that punk Gil Ho Se is the one.
سيدتي، أعتقد أن هذا البانك جيل هو سي هو الشخص المناسب.
Understood.
مفهومة.
[Driver Gil Ho Se]
[السائق جيل هو سي]
[Ms. Bu Se Mi] Sir, could you come to our house by nine?
[السيدة بو سي مي] سيدي، هل يمكنك الحضور إلى منزلنا بحلول الساعة التاسعة؟
I have a favor to ask.
عندي طلب أريد أن أطلبه.
This is good.
هذا جيد.
Enjoy your meal.
أتمنى لك وجبة شهية.
Ho Se!
هو سي!
Come here and have a drink with me!
تعال هنا وشرب مشروبًا معي!
I'll just go to the bathroom quickly.
سأذهب إلى الحمام بسرعة.
- Make it quick. - Okay.
- اجعلها سريعة. - حسنًا.
- We're out of alcohol. - Oh, right.
- لقد نفد الكحول منا. - أوه، صحيح.
I...
أنا...
No.
لا.
I don't think that way.
لا أعتقد بهذه الطريقة.
Wait, look.
انتظر، انظر.
Our pretty Jeong Hwa, how could he...
جونغ هوا الجميل، كيف يمكنه...
- Honestly, I... - Principal.
- بصراحة أنا... - مدير المدرسة.
- Yes? - Where's Ms. Bu Se Mi?
- نعم؟ - أين السيدة بو سي مي؟
- I... - Huh?
- أنا... - هاه؟
Wait,
انتظر،
she was here just a moment ago.
لقد كانت هنا منذ لحظة.
Where did she go?
أين ذهبت؟
- Why? What's wrong? - Actually.
- لماذا؟ ما المشكلة؟ - في الحقيقة.
Honestly, I like Jeong Woo.
بصراحة، أنا أحب جونغ وو.
- I... - I like Jeong Woo.
- أنا... - أنا أحب جونغ وو.
Jeong Woo's nice.
جونغ وو لطيف.
He's such a kind person.
إنه شخص لطيف للغاية.
Jeong Woo... Jeong Woo?
جونغ وو... جونغ وو؟
Jeong Woo, don't you remember that?
جونغ وو، ألا تتذكر ذلك؟
Oh, it's fun.
أوه، إنه ممتع.
- Mi Seon. - Oh, Tae Min.
- مي سون. - أوه، تاي مين.
Where's Hye Ji?
أين هيه جي؟
She wanted vanilla ice cream earlier.
لقد أرادت آيس كريم الفانيليا في وقت سابق.
Huh? Hye Ji's right here.
هاه؟ هيجي هنا.
- Look. - Wait a minute.
- انظر. - انتظر دقيقة.
No, she's right here, Tae Min.
لا، إنها هنا، تاي مين.
Hye Ji's right here.
هيه جي هنا.
Just give it to her here.
فقط أعطها لها هنا.
- That's Hye Ji's. - Okay, Hye Ji.
- هذه هيه جي. - حسنًا، هيه جي.
Hye Ji who loves vanilla.
هيه جي التي تحب الفانيليا.
Give me some too.
أعطني بعضًا أيضًا.
By the way, earlier,
بالمناسبة، في وقت سابق،
you asked if he was limping, right?
لقد سألته إذا كان يعرج، أليس كذلك؟
Are you talking about that driver?
هل تتحدث عن هذا السائق؟
Yes, only recent newcomers to Muchang
نعم، فقط الوافدين الجدد إلى موتشانج
are the driver and seasonal farm workers.
هم السائقون والعمال الزراعيون الموسميون.
Since Jeong Woo's acting this way...
بما أن جونغ وو يتصرف بهذه الطريقة...
- Mi Seon, Mi Seon. - Huh?
- مي سون، مي سون. - هاه؟
Where'd Mr. Gil go?
أين ذهب السيد جيل؟
Mr. Gil?
السيد جيل؟
He must be somewhere.
لابد أنه في مكان ما.
Oh, Ho Se?
أوه، ماذا؟
He went to the bathroom to pee earlier.
ذهب إلى الحمام للتبول في وقت سابق.
Where did he go?
أين ذهب؟
If he went to pee, he's in the bathroom. Why keep looking elsewhere?
إذا ذهب للتبول، فهو في الحمام. لماذا يبحث في مكان آخر؟
Dong Min, what's wrong?
دونغ مين، ما الخطب؟
Dong Min.
دونغ مين.
Dong Min!
دونغ مين!
Ms. Bu Se Mi.
السيدة بو سي مي.
Who exactly are you?
من أنت بالضبط؟
Miss, calm down.
آنسة، اهدئي.
[Jeon Dong Min]
[جيون دونغ مين]
Friend! Are you okay?
صديقي! هل أنت بخير؟
Snap out of it, friend!
استيقظ من هذا، يا صديقي!
Can you see me?
هل بإمكانك رؤيتي؟
Yeong Ran, are you hurt?
يونغ ران، هل أنت مصاب؟
Hye Ji.
هيه جي.
Baek Hye Ji.
بايك هيه جي.
No.
لا.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Ms. Bu Se Mi.
السيدة بو سي مي.
♫ Starting to be born again ♫
♫ البدء في الولادة من جديد ♫
♫ Now is the time ♫
♫ الآن هو الوقت ♫
♫ Even hidden scars will shine ♫
♫ حتى الندوب المخفية سوف تلمع ♫
♫ I share the light ♫
♫ أنا أشارك النور ♫
♫ I'll brighten the days shrouded in darkness ♫
♫ سأضيء الأيام التي يكتنفها الظلام ♫
This was Gil Ho Se's room.
كانت هذه غرفة جيل هو سي.
There must be something here.
لا بد أن يكون هناك شيء هنا.
Lee Mi Seon, principal of Iseon Kindergarten.
لي مي سون، مديرة روضة إيسيون.
Let's not involve family.
دعونا لا نشرك العائلة.
Let me make a proposal.
دعني أقدم اقتراحًا.
Doctor!
طبيب!
In exchange for that proposal, how much will you give me?
في مقابل هذا العرض، كم ستعطيني؟
As much as you want.
بقدر ما تريد.
You miss Ms. Bu Se Mi a lot, right?
أنت تفتقد السيدة بو سي مي كثيرًا، أليس كذلك؟
I have something to say.
عندي شيء أريد قوله.
I've missed you.
لقد افتقدتك.
Huh? What?
هاه؟ ماذا؟
Even if everything fails,
حتى لو فشل كل شيء،
I'll kill Ga Seon Yeong myself then.
سأقتل جا سون يونغ بنفسي إذن.
[Gaseong Group Emergency Press Conference] You'll never be able to go back to your old life.
[المؤتمر الصحفي الطارئ لمجموعة جاسونغ] لن تتمكن أبدًا من العودة إلى حياتك القديمة.